<!-- 
TODO:


-->

14.03:
Added Quern for grinding resources without research

14.02:
Copper tiles no longer conflict with Industrialisation copper tiles

14.01:
Fixed chandelier placement for A14

14.00:
Updated to A14
Reduced well crafting time
Changed racks sizes to be 1x1, redrew graphics, adjusted stats
Added universal rack for storing just about everything - fancier than a 1x1 stockpile
Mudbricks require sand or clay
Building_Upgradable changed to CompUpgradeable for more usability
Added rubberized asphalt, terrain with enhanced move speed
Added clay recipe
Imported windows from POW
Added traders selling copper and rubber
Added furnace - allows for utility cooking recipes that don't belong at a stove
Added anti-fatigue mats - rubber mats to stand at while working. Provides comfort and boosts cleanliness
Colonists can look out windows to gain joy. Colonists with cabin fever gain more joy
Chandeliers can be traded with furniture traders
Vent is toggleable - control whether or not to allow air to equalize
Spectago grows in the wild


<!-- Alpha 13 and lesser versions -->

v13.3:
Copper spawns scattered around the map at worldgen
Tweaked mudbrick stats
Added Clay, dug up in shallow water or marshy soil
Clay replaces sand in mudbrick recipe
Added brick recipe
Reduced skill requirement for making mudbricks
Added glass
Added ItemSpawner - spawns a random quantity of a given item
Increased quartz commonality, quartz drops 8-35 pieces when mined
Added SafeToRemoveDefs - A set of folders to easily remove certain features that are not used by other mods
Fixed sink not properly updating room cleanliness
Fixed sink not giving cleaned thoughts to colonists
Added Building_Upgradable - allows WorkTables to be upgraded, optionally requiring research to do so

v13.2:
Added Copper
Added Quartz, Fused quartz
Added CompSunlight WeatherLight getter - reports weather light levels as Bright, Darkened, Dark, or None
Added CompSunlight.SimpleFactoredSunlight, identical to old FactoredSunlight
CompSunlight.FactoredSunlight now updates sunlight values
Added xml commenting to C# code
From ZEN: Added Gravel
Added Sand and Dirt
Added vanilla override using sand for sandbags
Added mudbricks, stone blocks crafted using dirt, sand, and hay
Added drying mudbricks, building allowing mudbricks to dry in the sunlight



v13.1:
New Additions:
	Added Sink - boosts room cleanliness. Uses fresh water as fuel

Mod Utilities:
	Added CompColdPusher
	Added CompProperties_ColdPusher
	Added CompRainTank
	Added CompSunlight
	Added PlaceWorker_AgainstWall
	Added PlaceWorker_NotUnderThickRoof


From CPD:
	Added Fresh water bucket
	Added Well
	Added Food rack
	Added Bottled water
	Removed bucket recipe, bucket is now an implied item.
	Water can now be bottled at the Simple crafting table
	
From POW:
	Added Simple crafting table
	Added Wooden vent
	Added Individual table
	Added Stump chair
	
From AJO:
	Added Spectago/Rainbow petals
	
From RPH:
	Added Medicine rack